<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>azinudinachzab.github.io</title>
    <link>https://azinudinachzab.github.io/tags/hello-world/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on azinudinachzab.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016 Azinudin Achzab Design credit: </copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://azinudinachzab.github.io/tags/hello-world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://azinudinachzab.github.io/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 23:55:48 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azinudinachzab.github.io/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;Hello World!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;(This is my first time writing in english, so if you look some confusing word or grammar forgive me and just bear with it)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, github said:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;The Hello World project is a time-honored tradition in computer programming. It is a simple exercise that gets you started when learning something new.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m intended to start my blog Hello World project today. But im asian, self-introducing and greetings are a must tradition when you meet a new society. So, it’s a good thing if i could killing 2 birds with 1 stone, i’ll introduce myself and do my blog Hello World project in this writing.
My name is Azinudin Achzab, you can call me Azin, Udin or anything you want as long it’s a good nickname. I just an ordinary boy who try to be an extraordinary boy. I’m suck at everything but at least i try hard and harder to be an AAA Game Developer even though i knew i’ll just become a loser in the end.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not a pessimistic jerk, i just tell the truth that all of us are a loser in some way. For example, Mark, Bill Gates and Steve Jobs are loser in the eyes of Harvard’s graduates. But the society thought they are a success entrepreneurs. Loser is just a perspective matters, maybe you could see me as a good writer or creative boy but in my eyes i just a loser.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to the red string, i just finished my efforts to do a personal-branding (thats what my lecturer said) made a github account, made a personal blog, published my story in medium and share my public socmed accounts everywhere in the internet. I did it all because it is a way to become closer and closer to developer life at least if i’m not become a developer in the end i could close to it even just a little.
And you must know the fact that i can do a coding is because i am a student on a state university, my major is computer for education. It’s not like i learn HTML, Java, PHP, Pascal, etc because i liked it, i learned it because i have to do it and i hate the fact that i aimed to be a teacher when i graduated. Becoming a game developer is just a thing i want to do.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before the last line i want you to know that my age is 20th, my bloodtype is A, i am a straight male and my hobby is sleep. I lived in Tangerang Selatan but temporaly i lived in Surakarta/Solo (Jokowi’s born land) because of my study. You can come along take a sip of Angkringan Coffe and do a nice chit-chat with me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dont worry about me just worry about yourself, i’m always happy undergo my life even i don’t have a clear path. Nice to meet you! In the end of the words,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Hello World!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@eskadia/hello-world-454e55732a2#.b3rsd7pwv&#34;&gt;https://medium.com/@eskadia/hello-world-454e55732a2#.b3rsd7pwv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>